Register of the Albert C. Wedemeyer papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1927-1988 (Boxes 24-70)
  - Lawrence, George W., 1959-1979 (Box-folder 46: 20)
  - Laxalt, Paul, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 46: 21)
  - Lazo, Mario, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 46: 22)
  - Leahy, William D., 1953 (Box-folder 46: 23)
  - Lebor, John F., 1966-1969 (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - Lee, Chong Hak, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 47: 2)
  - Lee, David T., 1984-1988 (Box-folder 47: 3)
  - Lee, J. Bracken, 1951-1956 (Box-folder 47: 4)
  - Lee, John, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 47: 5)
  - Lee, Orient, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 47: 6)
  - Lee, Pearson P. S., 1973-1986 (Box-folder 47: 7)
  - Lee, Russel V., 1969-1982 (Box-folder 47: 8)
  - Lee, Teng-hui, 1988 (Box-folder 47: 9)
  - Lefler, William B., 1976-1988 (Box-folder 47: 10)
  - Lehleitner, George H., 1966-1983 (Box-folder 47: 11)
  - Leisure, George S., 1967 (Box-folder 47: 12)
  - Lemnitzer, Louis Lyman, 1957-1987 (Box-folder 47: 13)
  - Lenczowski, John, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 47: 14)
  - Leung, Ting-man, 1966 (Box-folder 47: 15)
  - Levine, Isaac Don, 1956-1981 (Box-folder 47: 16)
  - Levings, Nelson T., 1957-1967 (Box-folder 47: 17)
  - Lewis, Boyd, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 47: 18)
  - Lewis, Fulton, Jr., 1957 (Box-folder 47: 19)
  - Lewis, Roger, 1970 (Box-folder 47: 20)
  - Li, K. T., 1965-1982 (Box-folder 47: 21)
  - Liberty Lobby, 1963-1979 (Box-folder 47: 22)
    See also: CORRESPONDENCE/Dall, Curtis.
  - Liddell Hart, B. H., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 47: 23)
  - Liebman, Marvin, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 47: 24)
  - Ligutti, L. G., 1975-1981 (Box-folder 47: 25)
  - Lilienthal, Alfred, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 47: 26)
  - Lin, Yu-tang, 1961 (Box-folder 47: 27)
  - Lincoln, G. A., 1953-1974 (Box-folder 47: 28)
    Includes speeches and writings by Lincoln.
  - Lincoln, Lawrence J., 1973-1974 (Box-folder 47: 29)
  - Lincoln Center for Legal Studies, 1978 (Box-folder 47: 30)
  - Lindbergh, Charles, 1959-1972 (Box-folder 47: 31)
  - Lindley, Don E., 1981-1988 (Box-folder 47: 32)
  - Linebarger, Paul, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 47: 33)
  - Littell, Norman M., 1971-1975 (Box-folder 47: 34)
  - Little, Brown and Company, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 47: 35)
  - Liu, Frederick F., 1959-1965 (Box-folder 47: 36)
  - Liu, Hoh-to and Julia, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 47: 37)
  - Liu, Johnson, 1965-1980 (Box-folder 47: 38)
  - Loeb, William and Nackey S., 1965-1988 (Box-folder 47: 39)
  - Lohbeck, Donald, 1964 (Box-folder 47: 40)
  - Lombard, Charles F., 1968-1976 (Box-folder 47: 41)
  - London, Dan, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 47: 42)
  - Long, Hamilton A., 1982 (Box-folder 47: 43)
  - Longacre, David R., 1965-1968 (Box-folder 47: 44)
  - Loper, Herbert B., 1956-1970 (Box-folder 47: 45)
  - Loringhoven, Elizabeth Freytag, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 48: 1)
  - Lovink, A. H. J., 1954-1959 (Box-folder 48: 2)
  - Lowry, Charles, 1953-1988 (Box-folder 48: 3-4)
    Includes printed material relating to the Foundation for Religious Action in the Social and Civil Order, writings by Lowry, and correspondence with Jesse Helms, Norman Vincent Peale and others.
  - Lutes, LeRoy, Jr., 1962-1982 (Box-folder 48: 5)
  - Lyon, John B., 1962-1968 (Box-folder 48: 6)
  - Lyons, Daniel, 1968 (Box-folder 48: 7)
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1951 (Box-folder 48: 8)
  - M - General, 1951-1988 (Box-folder 48: 9-11)
  - Ma, Carl C. H., 1973-1980 (Box-folder 48: 12)
  - McAfee, William, 1953-1964 (Box-folder 48: 13)
  - MacArthur, Douglas and Jean, 1958-1980 (Box-folder 49: 1)
  - McArthur, Edwin, 1964-1984 (Box-folder 49: 2)
  - McAuliffe, A. C., 1964-1976 (Box-folder 49: 3)
  - McBain, Hughston M., 1956-1976 (Box-folder 49: 4)
  - McBride, Robert B., 1962-1982 (Box-folder 49: 5)
  - McCarthy, Frank, 1970-1983 (Box-folder 49: 6)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, 1953 (Box-folder 49: 7)
  - McCarty, John T., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 49: 8)
  - McClellan, John L., 1959-1972 (Box-folder 49: 9)
  - McClure, Mark, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 49: 10)
  - McClure, Robert and Eve, 1953-1981 (Box-folder 49: 11)
  - McCollister, John Y., 1972-1976 (Box-folder 49: 12)
  - McConaughy, Walter, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 49: 13)
  - McConnell, Fenton and Mary [Knight], 1955-1983 (Box-folder 49: 14)
  - McConnell, Raymond, 1951-1957 (Box-folder 49: 15)
  - McConnell, Sally, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 49: 16)
  - McCormick, R. Chesley, 1956-1986 (Box-folder 49: 17-19)
  - McCrea, Joel, 1961 (Box-folder 50: 1)
  - McCrea, John L., 1974 (Box-folder 50: 2)
  - MacDonald, Charles B., 1976-1981 (Box-folder 50: 3)
  - McDougald, John A., 1962-1985 (Box-folder 50: 4)
  - McDowell, Robert H., 1974 (Box-folder 50: 5)
  - McFarland, Elaine, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 50: 6)
  - McFarlane, Robert C., 1986 (Box-folder 50: 7)
  - McFee, Madeline, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 50: 8)
  - McGhee, George C., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 50: 9)
  - McGowan, M. M., 1956 (Box-folder 50: 10)
  - McGovern, George S., 1966-1977 (Box-folder 50: 11)
  - McHugh, Raymond, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 50: 12)
  - McKay, Douglas, 1953 (Box-folder 50: 13)
  - McKnight, Mary, 1964-1977 (Box-folder 50: 14)
  - McLean, David S. and Marjorie, 1971-1988 (Box-folder 50: 15)
  - McMahon, William D., 1963-1987 (Box-folder 50: 16)
  - McNamee, Roland and Emily, 1955-1988 (Box-folder 50: 17)
  - McNeese, A. G., Jr., 1962-1982 (Box-folder 50: 18)
  - McNulty, John J., 1962-1965 (Box-folder 50: 19)
  - Maddocks, Ray T. and family, 1957-1973 (Box-folder 50: 20)
  - Magruder, Carter B., 1961 (Box-folder 50: 21)
  - Mahon, George H., 1964-1979 (Box-folder 50: 22)
  - Makinney, Fred W., 1967-1969 (Box-folder 50: 23)
  - Malone, Wallace D., 1962-1967 (Box-folder 50: 24)
  - Malsch, Erna, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 50: 25)
  - Mandel, Marvin, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 50: 26)
  - Manion, Clarence E., 1958-1979 (Box-folder 50: 27)
  - Manly, Chesly, 1958 (Box-folder 50: 28)
  - Manning, John, 1956 (Box-folder 50: 29)
  - Mansfield, Mike, 1962 (Box-folder 50: 30)
  - Manson, Daniel, 1976-1987 (Box-folder 50: 31)
  - Manteuffel, Hasso von, 1972 (Box-folder 50: 32)
  - Mao, Paul Cheng-tzu, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 50: 33)
  - Mardikian, George, 1958-1977 (Box-folder 50: 34)
    Includes printed material, and letters by Richard Nixon.
  - Marlow, Fred, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 51: 1)
  - Marshall, Katherine (Mrs. George C. Marshall), 1967 (Box-folder 51: 2)
  - Marshall, Robert, 1970 (Box-folder 51: 3)
  - Marshall Group, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 51: 4)
  - Martin, David T., 1973-1984 (Box-folder 51: 5)
  - Martin, Joseph W., Jr., 1952 (Box-folder 51: 6)
  - Martin, Orville Wells, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 51: 7)
  - Martin, Paul and Kay, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 51: 8)
    Includes writings by Paul Martin.
  - Martin, Rose L., 1967-1978 (Box-folder 51: 9)
  - Martin, William McC., 1958-1969 (Box-folder 51: 10)
  - Mary Magdalen, Sister, 1958-1985 (Box-folder 51: 11)
  - Mason, Frank E., 1951-1979 (Box-folder 51: 12-13)
    Includes correspondence with William F. Buckley, Raymond Moley, James Stahlman, Ivan Yeaton and others.
  - Mathews, William, 1958 (Box-folder 51: 14)
  - Mathias, Charles, 1986 (Box-folder 51: 15)
  - Mattei, A. C., 1957 (Box-folder 51: 16)
  - Mayo, C. W., 1958 (Box-folder 51: 17)
  - Maytag, Lewis B. and Marquita, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 51: 18)
  - Mele [Hall], Marianne, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 51: 19)
  - Mellenthin, Horst von, 1956-1977 (Box-folder 51: 20)
  - Meloy, Guy S., 1963 (Box-folder 51: 21)
  - Mendell, Mike, 1964-1978 (Box-folder 51: 22)
  - Menhennet, Kitty Kean, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 51: 23)
    See also: CORRESPONDENCE/Hutchin, Claire and Kitty.
  - Menjou, Adolphe, 1952-1960 (Box-folder 51: 24)
  - Menke, John L., 1974-1975 (Box-folder 51: 25)
  - Menninger, William C., 1959-1966 (Box-folder 51: 26)
  - Merkle, Bruce F., 1973-1983 (Box-folder 51: 27)
  - Metcalfe, Arthur G. B., 1973 (Box-folder 51: 28)
  - Meyer, Paul W., 1964-1967 (Box-folder 51: 29)
  - Milbank, Jeremiah, 1956-1972 (Box-folder 51: 30)
  - Millen, Jonathan A., II, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 51: 31)
  - Miller, Alice M., 1951-1959 (Box-folder 51: 32)
  - Miller, Jack, 1963 (Box-folder 51: 33)
  - Miller, JoZach, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 51: 34)
  - Miller, Luther D., 1967-1985 (Box-folder 51: 35)
  - Miller, Virgil, 1968-1982 (Box-folder 51: 36)
  - Miller, William E., 1962-1964 (Box-folder 51: 37)
  - Mitchell, Robert F., 1967-1976 (Box-folder 52: 1)
  - Mixson, James M., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 52: 2)
  - Moffat, Donald R., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 52: 3)
  - Moley, Raymond, 1956-1964 (Box-folder 52: 4)
  - Moloney, John A., 1975-1977 (Box-folder 52: 5)
  - Monahan, John W., 1972-1983 (Box-folder 52: 6)
  - Monteith, Stanley, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 52: 7)
  - Moody, Lucien B., 1958 (Box-folder 52: 8)
  - Moorer, Thomas H., 1971-1974 (Box-folder 52: 9)
  - Moore, Merrill, 1956-1964 (Box-folder 52: 10)
  - Moorman, Thomas J., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 52: 11)
  - Moreell, Ben, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 52: 12)
  - Morley, Felix, 1958-1964 (Box-folder 52: 13)
  - Morris, William Fuller, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 52: 14)
  - Morse, John H., 1964-1985 (Box-folder 52: 15)
  - Morse, Robert H., 1964-1973 (Box-folder 52: 16)
  - Morse, Wayne, 1966 (Box-folder 52: 17)
  - Mortensen, Ralph, 1975-1984 (Box-folder 52: 18)
  - Moseley, George V. H., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 52: 19)
  - Mosig, Carl, 1966 (Box-folder 52: 20)
  - Mountbatten, Louis, 1952-1979 (Box-folder 52: 21)
  - Mountbatten [Hicks], Patricia, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 52: 22)
  - Moy, Ernest K., 1951 (Box-folder 52: 23)
  - Muir, Dorothy T., 1956-1987 (Box-folder 52: 24)
    Includes letters by John Chamberlain and others.
  - Muir, James I., Jr., 1962-1968 (Box-folder 53: 1)
  - Muir, Malcolm, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 53: 2)
  - Mullen, Buell, 1956-1984 (Box-folder 53: 3)
  - Mundt, Karl, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 53: 4)
  - Munroe, Ralph, 1971 (Box-folder 53: 5)
  - Munson, Frederick P., 1976-1980 (Box-folder 53: 6)
  - Munson, Lyle H., 1968-1973 (Box-folder 53: 7)
  - Murphey, Henry S., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 53: 8)
  - Murphy, George, 1965-1980 (Box-folder 53: 9)
  - Murphy, Paul, 1960 (Box-folder 53: 10)
  - Murphy, Robert, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 53: 11)
  - Murray, Hyde H., 1984-1988 (Box-folder 53: 12)
  - Murrell, Nora, 1978 (Box-folder 53: 13)
  - N - General, 1962-1988 (Box-folder 53: 14)
  - National Strategy Information Center (Frank R. Barnett), 1968-1972 (Box-folder 53: 15)
  - National War College (E. T. Wooldridge), 1956-1957 (Box-folder 53: 16)
  - Neathery, Alicia, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 53: 17)
  - Nebraska Society, 1969 (Box-folder 53: 18)
  - Nelson, Donald H., 1980-1986 (Box-folder 53: 19)
  - Nemazee, Hassan, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 53: 20)
  - Neubaur Beck, Gertrude, 1958-1970 (Box-folder 53: 21)
  - Nevotti, Richard and Jane, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 53: 22)
  - New Leader (Sol Levitas), 1959 (Box-folder 53: 23)
  - New York Times, 1972 (Box-folder 53: 24)
  - Ney, Virgil, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 53: 25)
  - Neyland, R. R., 1959 (Box-folder 53: 26)
  - Nichols, Kenneth D., 1980-1987 (Box-folder 53: 27)
  - Niess, Oliver M., 1963 (Box-folder 53: 28)
  - Nimitz, Chester W. and Catherine, 1958-1969 (Box-folder 53: 29)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1958-1988 (Box-folder 53: 30)
    Includes speeches by Nixon, and letters by John Dean, Maurice Stans and others.
  - Noble, Charles H., 1976-1978 (Box-folder 53: 31)
  - Nonnenmacher, Nicholas T., 1962-1970 (Box-folder 53: 32)
  - North, Thomas, 1965-1985 (Box-folder 53: 33)
  - Nulsen, Marian (Mrs. Charles K.), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 53: 34)
  - Nygaard, Jack, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 53: 35)
  - O - General, 1953-1987 (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - O'Brien, Robert, 1976-1987 (Box-folder 54: 2)
  - Ochsner, Alton and Jane, 1963-1983 (Box-folder 54: 3-5)
  - O'Daniel, John W., 1964-1968 (Box-folder 54: 6)
  - Odell, Joseph C., 1977-1983 (Box-folder 54: 7)
  - O'Gara, Alfred and Betty, 1956-1983 (Box-folder 54: 8)
  - O'Gara, Gordon C., 1967-1969 (Box-folder 54: 9)
  - O'Hanlon, Pat, 1962-1978 (Box-folder 54: 10)
  - O'Hara, Thomas A., 1956-1959 (Box-folder 54: 11)
    Includes a letter by Dwight Eisenhower.
  - O'Hare, Joseph James and Bobbie, 1950-1977 (Box-folder 54: 12)
  - Olmstead, George, 1956-1985 (Box-folder 54: 13)
  - Olmstead, George, Jr., 1984 (Box-folder 54: 14)
  - Olofson, Darwin, 1966-1984 (Box-folder 55: 1)
    Includes writings by Olofson.
  - Olson, Charles and Shirley, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 55: 2)
  - O'Meara, Andrew P., 1979-1984 (Box-folder 55: 3)
  - Onacewicz, Wlodzimierz, 1962-1984 (Box-folder 55: 4)
  - O'Neil, James F., 1958-1974 (Box-folder 55: 5)
  - Osborne, Jim R., 1979-1988 (Box-folder 55: 6)
  - Osborne, Ray S. and Frances, 1965-1987 (Box-folder 55: 7)
  - Otto, Egbert, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 55: 8)
  - Ouang, Max and Eppy, 1968-1980 (Box-folder 55: 9)
  - Overby, Andrew, 1957-1984 (Box-folder 55: 10)
  - P - General, 1956-1987 (Box-folder 55: 11)
  - Packard, David, 1968-1988 (Box-folder 55: 12)
  - Paffenbarger, George and Rachel, 1969-1988 (Box-folder 55: 13)
  - Page, G. Nelson, 1964-1979 (Box-folder 55: 14)
  - Palm, Charles and Miriam, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 55: 15)
  - Palmer, Paul, 1958 (Box-folder 55: 16)
  - Papagos, Alexander, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 55: 17)
  - Papen, Franz von, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 55: 18)
  - Pappas, George, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 55: 19)
  - Pappenheim, Rudolf zu, 1965-1981 (Box-folder 55: 20)
  - Park, Chung Hee, 1970 (Box-folder 55: 21)
  - Parks, William R., 1968-1972 (Box-folder 55: 22)
  - Parmley, Loren F., 1967-1968 (Box-folder 55: 23)
  - Passman, Otto, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 55: 24)
  - Patterson, Edward, 1956-1985 (Box-folder 55: 25)
  - Pattison, Hal C., 1967-1970 (Box-folder 55: 26)
  - Paul VI, Pope, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 55: 27)
  - Pawley, William D., 1970 (Box-folder 55: 28)
  - Payne, F. Dana, 1970-1981 (Box-folder 55: 29)
  - Payne, Alberta and Eleanor, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 55: 30)
  - Peale, Norman Vincent, 1958 (Box-folder 55: 31)
  - Pee, Peter Tsong-kan, 1952-1984 (Box-folder 56: 1)
  - Pegler, Westbrook, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 56: 2)
  - Peirson, Sam, 1962-1984 (Box-folder 56: 3)
  - Pennoyer, Paul, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 56: 4)
  - Percy, Charles M., 1973 (Box-folder 56: 5)
  - Persons, Wilton B., 1954-1956 (Box-folder 56: 6)
  - Perwein, Al H., 1964-1980 (Box-folder 56: 7)
  - Peter, Prince of Greece and Denmark, undated (Box-folder 56: 8)
  - Peterson, Rudolph A., 1966 (Box-folder 56: 9)
  - Petley, George S., 1966-1967 (Box-folder 56: 10)
  - Pew, Joseph N., Jr., 1957-1963 (Box-folder 56: 11)
  - Pfeiffer, Edward J., 1976-1979 (Box-folder 56: 12)
  - Philion, Albert, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 56: 13)
  - Philippe, Claudius Charles, 1956-1962 (Box-folder 56: 14)
  - Phillips, Wendell, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 56: 15)
  - Phleger, Herman, 1953 (Box-folder 56: 16)
  - Pihl, Paul and Charlotte, 1962-1988 (Box-folder 56: 17)
  - Place, Stephen B., 1971 (Box-folder 56: 18)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 56: 19)
  - Poch, Robert A., 1966-1982 (Box-folder 56: 20)
  - Poeschel, Harold P., 1962-1985 (Box-folder 56: 21)
  - Pogue, Forrest C., 1957-1986 (Box-folder 56: 22)
  - Pogue, L. Welch, 1963-1988 (Box-folder 56: 23)
  - Porteus, James, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 56: 24)
    Includes letters by Husband Kimmel.
  - Porzelt, Paul, 1958 (Box-folder 56: 25)
  - Poudre, Lou, 1974-1984 (Box-folder 56: 26)
  - Power, Thomas S., 1963 (Box-folder 56: 27)
  - Pownall, Henry, undated (Box-folder 56: 28)
  - Pray, Max and Peg, 1956-1984 (Box-folder 56: 29)
  - Priest, Ivy Baker, 1953 (Box-folder 56: 30)
  - Private Sector Council, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 56: 31)
  - Pryor, Samuel F., 1965-1978 (Box-folder 56: 32)
  - Pugh, John R., 1957-1973 (Box-folder 56: 33)
  - Pulliam, Eugene C., 1963-1970 (Box-folder 57: 1)
  - Putnam, Carleton, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 57: 2)
  - Pyke, Frederick M., 1974-1979 (Box-folder 57: 3)
  - Pyke, James H., 1961 (Box-folder 57: 4)
  - Q - General, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 57: 5)
  - Quinn, Terence J., 1965 (Box-folder 57: 6)
  - R - General, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 57: 7-8)
  - Raborn, W. F., 1966 (Box-folder 57: 9)
  - Radford, Arthur, 1953 (Box-folder 57: 10)
  - Raeburn, Abner and Margie, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 57: 11)
  - Raeburn, Richard M., 1965-1968 (Box-folder 57: 12)
  - Raeburn, Robert A., 1970-1988 (Box-folder 57: 13)
  - Rahim, Hussein K., 1984 (Box-folder 57: 14)
  - Rahim, Kamil Abdul and Anna, 1953-1984 (Box-folder 57: 15)
  - Rainey, Marjorie, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 57: 16)
  - Randall, Russell, 1973 (Box-folder 57: 17)
  - Ratay, John P. and Gertrude, 1956-1984 (Box-folder 57: 18)
  - Ravenholt, Albert V., 1973-1974 (Box-folder 57: 19)
  - Readers Digest (Hobart Lewis, James Monahan, De Witt Wallace and others), 1952-1984 (Box-folder 57: 20)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1968-1988 (Box-folder 57: 21)
  - Reeder, Red, 1964-1985 (Box-folder 57: 22)
  - Rehnquist, George R., 1979-1983 (Box-folder 57: 23)
  - Reid, Doris Fielding, 1962-1972 (Box-folder 57: 24)
  - Reid, William P., 1962-1971 (Box-folder 57: 25)
  - Reilly, Frank J. and Lee, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 57: 26)
  - Revera, Joan, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - Rex, Harry M., 1982-1983 (Box-folder 58: 2)
  - Rhee, Syngman, 1953-1965 (Box-folder 58: 3)
  - Rheem, Richard S., 1956-1966 (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - Rheem Manufacturing Company, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 58: 5)
  - Rhodes, John J., 1978 (Box-folder 58: 6)
  - Rich, William, 1983 (Box-folder 58: 7)
  - Richards, Victor, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 58: 8)
  - Richey, Harold L., 1956-1986 (Box-folder 58: 9)
  - Rickenbacker, Edward M., 1955-1971 (Box-folder 58: 10)
  - Rickover, Hyman G., 1978 (Box-folder 58: 11)
  - Riegle, Robert Dee, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 58: 12)
  - Rimanoczy, Richard S., 1962-1975 (Box-folder 58: 13)
  - Rivers, L. Mendel, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 58: 14)
  - Robb, Roger, 1965 (Box-folder 58: 15)
  - Roberts, Eugene B., 1974 (Box-folder 58: 16)
  - Robertson, Walter and Mary, 1956-1985 (Box-folder 58: 17)
  - Robie, Wendell, 1972 (Box-folder 58: 18)
  - Robinett, P. M., 1959 (Box-folder 58: 19)
  - Robinson, Frances, 1970-1988 (Box-folder 58: 20)
  - Rockafellow, Margaret, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 58: 21)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1958 (Box-folder 58: 22)
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1970 (Box-folder 58: 23)
  - Rockford College Institute, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 58: 24)
  - Rogers, Bernard W., 1979 (Box-folder 58: 25)
  - Rogers, James D., 1975-1979 (Box-folder 58: 26)
  - Rogers, William P., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 58: 27)
  - Roosevelt, Archibald B., 1962-1970 (Box-folder 58: 28)
  - Roosma, John S., 1964-1986 (Box-folder 58: 29)
  - Roots, John M., 1959-1988 (Box-folder 58: 30)
  - Rose Louise, Sister, 1970-1985 (Box-folder 58: 31)
  - Rosenberg, Elliot, 1970-1988 (Box-folder 58: 32)
  - Ross, Harold D. and Andrew, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 58: 33)
  - Rossbach, Gerhard, 1937-1962 (Box-folder 58: 34)
  - Rountree, Martha, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 58: 35)
  - Rowe, David, 1960-1971 (Box-folder 58: 36)
  - Rowe, J. Blanche, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 58: 37)
  - Rowe, Stanley M., 1964-1966 (Box-folder 58: 38)
  - Royall, Kenneth, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 58: 39)
  - Royen, Marmie, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - Rudinger, Elizabeth, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 59: 2)
  - Rumbaugh, James H., 1987-1988 (Box-folder 59: 3)
  - Rusk, Dean, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 59: 4)
  - Russell, Edward, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 59: 5)
  - Russell, Hubbard S., 1956-1964 (Box-folder 59: 6)
  - Russell, Richard, 1953-1969 (Box-folder 59: 7)
  - Rutledge, Paul W., 1960 (Box-folder 59: 8)
  - Ryan, C. E., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 59: 9)
  - Ryan, John L., Jr., 1963 (Box-folder 59: 10)
  - Ryan, Patrick J., 1963-1967 (Box-folder 59: 11)
  - Ryan, William F., 1963-1971 (Box-folder 59: 12)
  - S - General, 1956-1988 (Box-folder 59: 13-15)
  - Sabin, L. S., 1963-1985 (Box-folder 59: 16)
  - Sarnoff, David, 1955-1964 (Box-folder 59: 17)
  - Sater, Kathie, 1958-1983 (Box-folder 59: 18)
  - Saud al Faisal, 1977 (Box-folder 59: 19)
  - Saunders, A. E., 1964 (Box-folder 59: 20)
  - Schaefer, J. E., 1953-1969 (Box-folder 59: 21)
  - Schenken, John, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 59: 22)
  - Schindler, Paul E., Jr., 1979-1983 (Box-folder 59: 23)
  - Schlafly, Fred and Phyllis, 1964-1982 (Box-folder 59: 24)
  - Schlesinger, James R., 1975 (Box-folder 59: 25)
  - Schluter, F. E., 1973-1984 (Box-folder 60: 1)
    Includes writings by Schluter.
  - Schmidt, Frank H., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 60: 2)
  - Schmidt, Fred C., 1979-1982 (Box-folder 60: 3)
  - Schnyder, Felix, 1971 (Box-folder 60: 4)
  - Schulthess, Dieter von, 1972-1981 (Box-folder 60: 5)
  - Schulze, Franz-Joseph, 1979 (Box-folder 60: 6)
  - Schwarzkopf, Chet, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 60: 7)
  - Scott, Owen L., 1971-1975 (Box-folder 60: 8)
  - Scott, Stanley H., 1975-1976 (Box-folder 60: 9)
  - Seaman, Jonathan O., 1968-1971 (Box-folder 60: 10)
  - Sebald, William J., 1967-1972 (Box-folder 60: 11)
  - Sebree, Edmund B., 1958-1966 (Box-folder 60: 12)
  - Seedlock, Robert F., 1962-1988 (Box-folder 60: 13)
  - Seno, Sadao, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 60: 14)
    Includes an article by Seno.
  - Sergievsky, Boris, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 60: 15)
  - Sessions, Edgar H., 1968-1983 (Box-folder 60: 16)
  - Settle, Thomas G. W., 1962-1976 (Box-folder 60: 17)
  - Seward, John R., 1981-1985 (Box-folder 60: 18)
  - Shah, Konsin, 1965-1985 (Box-folder 60: 19)
    Includes writings by Shah.
  - Shen, James Chang-huan, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 60: 20)
  - Shepherd, Lemuel C., Jr., 1958 (Box-folder 60: 21)
  - Shepley, James R., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 60: 22)
  - Sherrill, Fred G., 1966-1975 (Box-folder 60: 23)
  - Shih, Paul C. Y., 1966-1967 (Box-folder 60: 24)
  - Shockley, William, 1986 (Box-folder 60: 25)
  - Shreve, L. G., 1972-1985 (Box-folder 60: 26)
  - Sibley, Alden K., 1957-1980 (Box-folder 60: 27)
  - Sidey, Hugh, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 60: 28)
  - Siegrist, Robert, 1958-1975 (Box-folder 60: 29)
    Includes writings by Siegrist.
  - Sih, Paul K. T., 1968-1978 (Box-folder 60: 30)
  - Sikorsky, Igor I., 1966 (Box-folder 61: 1)
  - Silverthorn, M. H., 1984 (Box-folder 61: 2)
  - Simmons, Ray C., 1986-1987 (Box-folder 61: 3)
  - Simpson, William Hood, 1966-1981 (Box-folder 61: 4)
  - Sino-American Amity Fund (Paul Chan, Clarence Cooke, and others), 1955-1979 (Box-folder 61: 5)
    See also: Yu-Pin, Paul.
  - Sisa, Stephen, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 61: 6)
  - Sites, James N., 1977-1985 (Box-folder 61: 7)
  - Sivert, Daniel P., 1981-1984 (Box-folder 61: 8)
  - Skousen, W. Cleon, 1961-1988 (Box-folder 61: 9)
  - Slaughter, Willis R., 1963-1975 (Box-folder 61: 10)
  - Smedberg, W. R., 1957-1984 (Box-folder 61: 11)
  - Smeed, Ralph, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 61: 12)
  - Smith, C. R., 1956-1973 (Box-folder 61: 13)
  - Smith, Charles F., 1962-1968 (Box-folder 61: 14)
  - Smith, Frank M., 1972-1982 (Box-folder 61: 15)
  - Smith, Herbert E., 1957-1965 (Box-folder 61: 16)
  - Smith, Lee, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 61: 17)
  - Smith, Robert W., 1963-1968 (Box-folder 61: 18)
  - Smith, Truman and Kay, 1956-1988 (Box-folder 61: 19)
  - Snow, John Howland, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 61: 20)
  - Sokolsky, George E., 1953-1962 (Box-folder 61: 21)
  - Sordoni, Andrew J., 1956-1963 (Box-folder 61: 22)
  - Sorley, L. Stone, Jr., 1977-1988 (Box-folder 61: 23)
  - Sourwine, Julien G., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 61: 24)
  - South Africa Foundation, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 61: 25)
  - Southwick, William E., 1983 (Box-folder 61: 26)
  - Southworth, William N., 1965-1967 (Box-folder 61: 27)
  - Sparks, Hayden, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 61: 28)
  - Speidel, Hans, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 61: 29)
    Includes writings by Speidel.
  - Spellman, Francis, 1953-1967 (Box-folder 61: 30)
  - Spivak, Lawrence E., 1957-1976 (Box-folder 62: 1)
  - Spray, David E., 1967-1970 (Box-folder 62: 2)
  - Sproul, Robert G., 1964 (Box-folder 62: 3)
  - Stackelberg, Garnett, 1956-1972 (Box-folder 62: 4)
  - Staedke, Helmut, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 62: 5)
  - Stahlman, James G., 1958-1976 (Box-folder 62: 6)
    Includes correspondence with Richard Nixon and others.
  - Stans, Maurice, 1969 (Box-folder 62: 7)
  - Starke, Hans, 1988 (Box-folder 62: 8)
  - Stassen, Harold E., 1951 (Box-folder 62: 9)